[
    {
        "index" : 0,
        "question" : "2 + 2",
        "answer" : "4"
    },
    {
        "index" : 1,
        "question" : "3 + 3",
        "answer" : "6"
    },
    { 
        "index" : 2,  
        "question" : "4 + 4",
        "answer" : "8"
    },
    {
        "index" : 3,  
        "question" : "7 x 48",
        "answer" : "336"
    },
    {
        "index" : 4,  
        "question" : "10 x 1",
        "answer" : "10"
    },
    {
        "index" : 5,  
        "question" : "7 x 28",        
        "answer" : "196"
    },
    {
        "index" : 6,  
        "question" : "2 x 139,231",
        "answer" : "278462"        
    },
    {
        "index" : 7,  
        "question" : "8 x 4",
        "answer" : "32"
    },
    {
        "index" : 8,  
        "question" : "561 x 10",
        "answer" : "5610"        
    },
    {
        "index" : 9,  
        "question" : "3 x 3",
        "answer" : "9"
    }
]